LJUBINKA CAVDAROVSKA

About

Highly motivated, detail-focused professional. A solutionoriented, an expert researcher and innovative problem solver.

A self-directed person who performs efficiently in a busy environment and handles many tasks simultaneously. Excellence in recruitment strategies, the planning process improvements, employee development, and compliance with company values, in order to understand the company's goals and culture.

A competent communicator with skills in developing initiatives that improve company success and growth.

Skills

- People Management,
- Office Management
- Collaborative approach,
- Analyzing Thinking,
- Responsible person,
- Leadership,
- Teamwork, and Coaching
- Open-minded person,
- Confidentiality
- Managing Projects,
- Negotiation skills,
- Organization skills

Experience

October 2022 - Present

Inellipse

Product Owner, Bitola

- plan and develop the Project idea.
- create and lead the dream team who will be responsible for the project
- monitoring the Project progress and the defined deadlines.
- solve issues that arise in the process
- to ensure Stakeholder satisfaction.
- -evaluating Project Performance.

Contact

- Bitola
- **℃** 078299757
- ljubinkacavdarovska@yahoo.com

October 2019 -October 2022

Karpa na Evropa

People and Culture Manager, Bitola

- one-on-one meeting with the owner, for important topics for the company
- defining open job position
- planning the budget for the events (weekly, monthly, annually)
- 1 per week making a plan for all important events; birthdays, anniversaries, baby showers, etc
- defining the advertisements for an open position in the company.
- in charge of the Culture Interview
- take part in the first 2 weeks of training with the new employee and present the company's core values, company concept of working, etc.
- enhance and support the company culture, and team spirit among all colleagues
- participates in creating the employee's policies, documentation,
- create a safe work environment
- manage employee benefits,
- manage 4 cross-functional teams, in 3 locations (USA, England, and Macedonia)

October 2018 -October 2019

Karpa na Evropa

Team Lead- Customer Loyalty Team, Bitola

- led a team of 11 team members -responsible for providing outstanding customer service by leading and motivating the Customer Support team,
- 1 per month developing loyalty programs to increase customer satisfaction
- 1 per week analyzing statistics and compiling accurate reports
- recruiting, mentoring, and developing customer service team members
- organizing and leading 2 team meetings per week

Education

St Kliment Ohridski University -Bitola

Faculty of Administration and Management of Information Systems

- Public Administration 2004-2008

Technical Skills

- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, Power Point)
- Google
- -Trello
- Jira
- Slack

Seminar and training

- Master in Digital Marketing Institute for Business and Management – Heidelberg Apr 2022- Feb 2023
- **Social Media Marketing**-Content Creation Lakeview Roscoe Village Chamber of Commerce- Jun 2022
- **HR of the future** Banister , Nov 2021
- **Trends of workspace culture** 2021 Zoom conference with Brigette Hyacinth Apr 2021
- **Global Leadership Summit** Skopje Nov 2019
- Global Leadership Summit -Skopje - Nov 2018

August 2017 -

Karpa na Evropa

December 2019 Customer Loyalty team-Bitola

- -the very first member of the Customer support team at MK
- 8 hours per day helping customers with complaints and questions,
- giving customers information about products and services,
- taking orders, and processing returns
- generating and developing new customers,
- identifying and assessing customer needs to achieve satisfaction

February 2017 - August 2017

Nelt Group Macedonia

Key Account Executive, Southwestern Macedonia

- preparing a sale plan including a forecast based on the targeted goal by aligning with the company goal
- planning strategy to acquire new customers with ambition and passion to achieve high results in order to maximize revenue and profit for enterprise sales through offering enterprise services
- meetings with Managers of big markets

April 2016 -August 2016

Rothstein International Development

Customer Service Representative, Bitola

- working with clients who have complaints, orders, or require information about products/services purchased from the organization
- providing solutions for every situation, and prioritizing the customers' needs at each step of the process